Hello friends, in this video we will talk
about ICICI LAD company.   The
company has today announced a dividend for its shareholders.  The
company has also given the dividend letter to NSC and BSE.
In this letter, the company has
clearly stated that it is
going to give a final dividend to its shareholders.   The
amount of dividend that they have fixed is
₹7 per equity share. Here the
company has fixed the amount of dividend.
But the company has not announced the record date and
payment date here.   The
company has said that the announcement of the record date will be made
at the upcoming Annual General Meeting.
As soon as the record date of the company is announced,
I will update you on my Telegram channel
and will also make a video on it on my channel.
So friends, a
big update has come out here for ICICI LBR shareholders.   The
company has announced a good dividend amount
for its shareholders.
If you are new to my channel then please
subscribe to the channel.  Dividend
related videos will continue to come like this in future also.
Thank you.